{
    "subject": "resource/Pink_Hope",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Organisation",
    "human_readable": "Pink Hope is an organisation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9746052622795105,
            "question": "What kind of organization is Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9149345755577087,
            "question": "Does Pink Hope collaborate with other organizations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8978367447853088,
            "question": "Are there any specific events or initiatives organized by Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7259623408317566,
            "question": "What are some of the services offered by Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6474878787994385,
            "question": "What does Pink Hope focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6445285677909851,
            "question": "Does Pink Hope operate in multiple locations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6238006353378296,
            "question": "How can individuals support Pink Hope's mission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190747618675232,
            "question": "Who does Pink Hope primarily help?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5251680016517639,
            "question": "What impact does Pink Hope aim to have on the community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47657856345176697,
            "question": "What are the core values of Pink Hope?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pink Hope is an organisation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5069_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact does Pink Hope aim to have on the community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5069_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who does Pink Hope primarily help?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5069_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can individuals support Pink Hope's mission?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5069_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5069_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Pink Hope is an organisation\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents associated with Pink Hope describe it as an organization, company, or hub that provides support and services for people at risk of breast and ovarian cancer."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly describe Pink Hope as an organization focused on supporting individuals to reduce their risk of hereditary cancer through education, support, and empowerment. Therefore, the statement that Pink Hope is an organization is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}